hey what's up I hope you had a great
holiday listen I want to talk about what
it's going to take to for you to make
the kind of money that you want to make
in 2025 moving forward I meet a lot of
coaches and mentors that they're not
bringing in the kind of clients they
want to make and so I want to walk you
through what's working right now what
you can do to start to bring in those
clients the truth is you got to learn
how to attract the right people that's
number one and then persuade those
people to buy your
programs here's the truth consumers are
Savvy they know when you're just trying
to sell them something and they know
when you're just sharing value quote
unquote to get them to buy something
truth is that that's exactly what I do
here on this YouTube channel is I share
value but I also share strategies that
work I believe that if you join my
accelerator program it's the best
program that's out there that helps
people get results and that it can get
you results as well but I want to give
you what's working right now that can
help you build your business
if you can figure out based on your
coaching Niche and how you help people
exactly what they desire so number one
you need to know what your Target
customer
desires more than anything
else you build your offer around their
desire you don't build it around what
they need and this is the key that you
need to understand for you to make the
kind of money that you want to make your
offer has to be based around what they
desire what they
want first you can deliver what they
need but you lead with what they desire
and the other side is is that most
people will not trust you on the
internet today because there's a lot of
people that are out there that are that
are just not worth their time plus now
we have ai we have YouTube we have a lot
of free resources that provide value to
people is that people don't want to make
an investment plus money is tight with a
lot of people economically they don't
want to make an investment into the
thing and so you have to build
trust and then you have to be able to
persuade persuade
people when you have that trust because
you can't persuade somebody unless they
trust you they have to trust and believe
that what you say you're going to do
that you'll be able to do for them I say
that I'm able to help people make six
figures starting out if they
consistently stick with me I can help
them make seven figures and even go to
eight figures if we work long term
because I've done it before I've helped
thousands of people start on this
journey and continue and it built
multiple businesses to the eight
figureure Mark and so with this is that
when somebody trusts that now my job is
how can I persuade them that if they
start working with me in my coaching
program that that is the result and
transformation that they are going to
get okay so you go based on the desired
result and transformation that somebody
has truth is they would have it already
if they knew how to get it but they
don't trust you because it's so hard for
them to get there the real desire that
somebody
has the re reason why they lack trust is
not because you did anything wrong it's
because it's been so hard for them to
get that desire already that you're
going up against
ingrained psychology that people have
that tells them this isn't for me I
can't have that people like me don't get
this I've tried that before I've tried
to make those things work before and
maybe you're watching this right now and
you're listening to me and you're
thinking that exact same thing about
your coaching business I made a lot of
people they they say that they're like
I've tried to grow this before and I
can't seem to get those
results so what you got to do is you got
to figure out okay that desire that they
can't get anywhere else that they've
been wanting that they are craving but
that they maybe have even given up on
and then your job is to build that trust
with them and persuade them to take
action now here's the
thing going into
2025 the last two years the ticktock
ification of the internet Tick Tock is
an app the ticktock
ification it has changed people's
psychology around how the Tik Tok
algorithm works even if you're on
Instagram you're not even on Tik Tok if
you're on Facebook or whatever you're on
people still react
respond the way that Tik Tock based
content is made and what is this
ticktock ification that's happened on
all forms of media on the Internet is is
high
dopamine and a lot of
sensationalism and because of that
people are way less likely to trust when
somebody's promising them something or
an offer that's out there okay as well
people's attention span is a lot lower
and this one's really big because two
years ago five years ago people would
sit through 50 minute
90 minute 2hour trainings no problem
they would sit through five day
challenges for free and then join and
pay thousands of dollars to join
programs five-day challenges 90-minute
webinars those still have value but most
people when they initially meet you
their attention
span is between a 20 to 40 minute
attention span when they initially meet
you
okay and and well and actually before
they initially meet you it's it's
actually about three to 10
seconds if you can build trust with
somebody at 3 to 10 seconds and there's
a ladder to this you build trust with
them for 3 to 10 seconds now they might
give you 3 to five minutes to read about
something that might be 20 to 40 minutes
long okay so they're going to read maybe
what that is that got their attention
they might read an email they might read
a landing page now you have this 20 to
40 minute offer right there what comes
above this now is anything that's two to
5 hours in length Okay and then up above
here can be 6 to 12
months and when we talk about 6 to 12
months that would be like weekly every
every month as far as that goes two to
five hours that could be either one hour
every week that could be an hour a day
but we end up stacking the attention
span of how long we're able to engage
with people so I wrote it all the way up
there how long people are willing to
stick with us in our ecos
system this is where we build that trust
with that that sort of like the
Instagram reels very short content and
now there's a new format as well that's
working really well on Instagram reals
and ads and this is something that
that's working like really good video
with text over the video is converting
like crazy more than anything else as
far as when it comes to ads goes overall
okay and so then from there we're able
to get people to want to spend a longer
length of time with us and it goes up
that ladder so what I recommend people
do is
create based on the desire that somebody
has
an
irresistible offer where people sign up
with an email address to get a 20 to 40
minute video presentation sent to them
and this is what we're using we're using
20 to 40 minute video presentations all
the time that we're going to send to our
email list uh and and and just one of
these videos might not convert to sales
they might not create the kind of
clients that we want to make so what we
do is we also utilize YouTube like this
to build and nurture that trust to
encourage people to spend more time with
us long term so like in my accelerator
program you know we offer a trial period
people can try it out um and you can by
the way check out the link below to see
how you can jump in there and and learn
how to get 10 to 20 brand new clients in
your coaching business every single
month there's a link in the description
below I'd love to encourage you to check
that out if you want to work a little
bit deeper with me and there's no cost
at all to to start with that so go check
that out as well in the description of
this video below here okay and so what
you want to do is you want to figure out
what is that thing that people desire
the
most how can you deliver that to people
in a condensed way that focuses in on
what what is the beginning steps the
beginning stages of what that person
needs
and desires to build that trust with you
what do they need not to get the
result but what do they need that's
going to build that trust those are two
very different things by the way because
if you're just telling people what's
going to get them the result truth is if
you lack the trust they're never going
to do it they're never going to buy into
it and and all of that it it serves to
validate yourself and many times that
can come out of the fear or worry that
people are going to be disappointed or
they're not going to like what you're
offering and that you have to overd
deliver to get people to trust you that
is not the case what it takes to
actually get people to trust you is to
make a connection emotionally and to
help shift the way that somebody is
thinking okay when we shift the way that
somebody's thinking it goes beyond just
telling people what to do we're tapping
into their do their drivers what is deep
beneath the surface that's driving them
to make decisions people make
decisions when
they emotionally buy into it not
logically emotionally they believe this
is going to get me the result that I
desire and it's always going to be based
on their desire and then the logic kicks
in to start to validate it they want to
see testimonies they want to see what's
included what's the price all of that
and and they start to spin it around
their head but the only way that you are
going to get somebody to sign up with
their name and email address and to
purchase your program is if you tap in
emotionally to what is going to drive
somebody to buy from you and that's
exactly what I work with people with in
our accelerator program is how do we
create those mechanisms that get people
to buy into when we say Buy in it's not
necessarily a financial buying it's that
they they are connecting with it they're
connecting emotionally with the outcome
they believe that it is going to produce
a result for them and now they are
willing to move a step forward with you
it's kind of like going on a second date
and a third date with you and so that's
what the goal is is if we can go out
there on social media find a wide net of
people and connect with them around a
very
specific desire that they have you find
as many people as possible that share
the same desire you you get them on your
email list you send them these 20 to 40
minute
videos and then from there you're able
to build trust with people
around exactly what it is that you offer
them once you do
this people will buy from you people
will become your clients people will
want to work with you now the next step
is you have to make a call to action you
have to tell them what that next step is
if they want to get started with you
there's a call to action like in the
description of this video below there's
a link that you can
take and get started on that journey of
working with me and find out how to get
10 to 20 brand new clients in your
business right there is a call to action
and I keep seeding it throughout the
video I keep mentioning what's the next
step that I want somebody to take and by
the way you can go check that out and
see how that process works how the
follow-up emails and all of that work
it's a it's a great case study for you
to check check out how we do this in our
business and it's producing massive
amount of results for us to help us get
more clients and to get people that work
with us okay and so that's exactly the
process that we need to learn going
into
2025 is we find the people we create
these Evergreen offers that grow our
email list we then move people to a
mechanism that's going to sell them on
our program
progams that creates the emotional Buy
in and then once the trust is built
there with the emotional buyin the
person will purchase because you've
increased their level of trust in you
your company the transformation you
deliver your product to a level 10 from
wherever they were starting at a lot of
people when they find you they're
they're at maybe a level like 3 to
five just the fact that they're
listening to you makes them a 3 to five
anybody lower than a three is not even
going to listen to you lower than a
three level
trust after they continue to listening
to you they might jump up to a six or a
seven but then as they get deeper into
your world and start getting immersed
maybe they get their questions answered
maybe they start to experience what it's
like to work with you as a professional
that delivers results with people and
they start to see how you've helped
other people do that that level of trust
starts to increase
but not all the way to a 10 you want to
get it to a level 10 and that will
happen after somebody engages with you
because you're able to then nurture them
with additional pieces of content you're
able to send them a message if you want
to to get to know them to understand
where they're at they could book a call
with you to understand where you can
start to learn how to help them you you
solve a immediate problem you figure out
what problem they need solve solved and
then you can create a custom sales
message for that specific person to sell
whatever your offer
is and so from there that's the process
of going from okay somebody's a random
person on the internet there's a ton of
them out there
to okay I found this thing I found this
information now I'm going to buy into it
and so by learning how to do those 20 to
40 minute videos that is what's going to
help you get the results in your
business these are like micro webinars
is how we do it so we break it down in a
in a very simple way is you provide
value with people you start to cast
vision for people as to where they're
going and at the end you become very
very confident to bridge the gap with
people as far
as what it takes to build trust and
create safety for them and this is one
of the key mechanisms that's important
to do throughout this process is to
create safety people buy because they
feel safe to actually purchase they feel
like they found somebody that is not
going to get them hurt they're not going
to lose money it's not going going to
cause a problem for them and as soon as
somebody feels safe in that interaction
to work with you as soon as that safety
is established and the trust is built
that's where the emotional driver comes
in that connects people and a lot of
coaches mentors trainers in their
presentations they're not creating that
safety with people they're not creating
that safe space where the client doesn't
have to feel like they have to perform
that they can just be who they are show
up as who they are and that's the thing
you want to be accepting of who people
are you know I found myself that I
struggled with that for the longest time
and it was one of the biggest things
where I was repelling good people
because I wasn't as accepting of where
people are at now I'm like listen like
wherever you're at I get it and I can
help you get to where you want to be
wherever that
is without any judgment and that's what
I love is being able to do that with
people and help them and guide them and
direct them and show them exactly how to
get from where they are to where they
want to be in their business okay so I'd
love to work with you in my accelerator
program again check out the link in the
description below let's get that Journey
started I'll see you in the next video
we'll talk soon a good one